Maggie Wilk

marzena.m.wilk@gmail.com | London

LinkedIn linkedin.com/in/maggie-wilk/ | **GitHub** github.com/Marzena-W **Portfolio** needs deployment

Summary

Creative graphic designer and passionate junior front-end developer who wants to learn and grow in a collaborative team environment. Over eight years of experience developing brands, products and engaging marketing materials. Skilled in HTML, CSS, and Adobe CC. A highly motivated individual who is eager to take on new challenges.

Skills

<u>Technical Skills:</u> HTML5, CSS3, Photoshop, InDesign, Illustrator, After Effect, AdobeXD, Figma, Bootstrap, React, GitHub, JavaScript, jQuery, JSON, AJAX, SQL, Git, Node.js

<u>Soft Skills:</u> Teamwork, Time Management, Communication, Self-motivation, Problem Solving, Creative thinking, Adaptability, Attention to detail, Quick learner

Projects

Park Time App | GitHub: https://github.com/Marzena-W/park-time-app/

- Summary: App showcasing chosen location on a map and current weather.
- Role: Designer & Developer
- Tools/Languages: JavaScript, API, HTML, CSS, Photoshop, Illustrator

Personal portfolio | GitHub: https://github.com/Marzena-W/planner-app

- Summary: A calendar application that saves events
- Role: Developer
- Tools/Languages: HTML, CSS, JavaScript

ReadMe Generator | GitHub: https://github.com/Marzena-W/readme-generator

- Summary: CLI app to auto-generate a readme from user input
- Role: Developer
- Tools/Languages: Node.js, JavaScript

Experience

Freelance Digital & Graphic Designer - April 2022 to present Maggie Wilk Design, London

- Advising clients on the best strategies to use for their projects.
- Experience with different mediums, such as print and digital, and understanding of technical specifications for each.
- Managing design projects from start to finish, including working with briefs, ideation, conception, design, and delivery.

Senior Graphic Designer/Marketing Coordinator - Jan 2020 to May 2022 Feme Ltd, London

- Developing website components through wireframing, prototyping and design.
- Collaborating with cross-functional teams (sales, copywriting, marketing, customer service) to develop and implement marketing strategies that aligned with business goals, target audience, and brand identity.
- Analysing data sets about customer complaints and introducing a process that improved the online shopping user experience.
- Developing website components through wireframing, prototyping and design.

Designer/Design Coordinator - Jun 2014 to Dec 2019 Feme Ltd, London

- Managing a team of 10+ members during multiple photoshoots.
- Conducting research and surveys, which helped to redesign a monthly magazine, resulting in a 45% increase in reading time of the digital issue.
- Serving as a creative guide for all key projects.
- Working on an average of 10+ projects weekly to engage with B2B and B2C customers.

Education

MSc, Physics (Computational physics) - University of Rzeszow Front-end Web Development Certificate - University of Birmingham

Other certifications

- Google Project Management: Professional Certificate, 2022 (Coursera)
- Google Foundations of User Experience (UX) Design, 2022 (Coursera)
- The Complete SQL Bootcamp, 2022 (Udemy)